Ofek Harpaz

Phone: 054-787-5579

Email: oharpaz1@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ofek-harpaz

GitHub: github.com/harpazofek

Profile:

An accomplished Technical Lead with a successful six-year track record in a start-up company developing Robotics solution.

Over the past year, I have expanded my expertise into DevOps, specializing in researching and integrating DevOps tools across large-scale Kubernetes clusters in multi-cloud environments (GCP, AWS).

Experience:

UtopiaTech - Ramat Gan • 2024 - PRESENT

DevOps Engineer

- Research and integrate DevOps technologies tools across multiple large scale kubernetes clusters across multi cloud environments (GCP, Helm, Kubernetes, AWS, Prometheus, Grafana, Custom Exporters)
- Develop, manage and automate full E2E CI/CD pipelines (GitLab)
- Manage kubernetes clusters, setup, automation of deployment processes with security orientation (GKE, Secrets, Encryption)
- Experience in Python and Bash scripting.
- Design and implement solution for dynamic cloud environments (containerized environments and microservices)

Fabric- Tel Aviv • 2018 - 2023

Technical Lead

- Managed full-cycle project implementation for new products integration and site setup, with a focus on problem management and escalation of hardware and software issues. (Linux, Ansible, Logs)
- Orchestrated cross-functional R&D initiatives to boost system performance in IL and US production environments. (Configuration Control, Monitoring, Performance)
- Directed and executed projects, overseeing local and international site installation processes.

Technical Support Specialist

- Performs diagnostics and comprehensive documentation of technical problems across diverse platforms.
- Directed technical teams in project execution, training, and provided comprehensive operational and technical product support.

Professional Service Engineer

• Deploy and integration of company product systems in the field

IDF- Air Force • 2012 - 2016

Electrical Technician - Team Leader

• Confidential - Expansion will be provided per request.

Key Skills:

DevOps Technologies:

Kubernetes, Helm, Docker, Ansible, GitLab, CloudFlare, Proton, Hostinger, Node, Jenkins, Namecheap

• Environments:

Linux, Windows, GCP, AWS

• Monitoring and Observability: Grafana, Prometheus, Custom

Exporters, Kibana

• Coding:

Python, Bash

• Hardware:

Robotics, Servers, PCB, Electronic

Languages:

Hebrew- Native English- Proficient

Education:

• DevOps Engineer

Bar-Ilan University 2022 - 2023

Electrical Technician

Ort College Full Matriculation + Electrical Tech diploma 2008 - 2012